Semenov Volodymyr

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Address

Ukraine, Kiev

Phone

+380 (63) 700 68 36 (Viber, WhatsApp, Telegram)

Email

trenersem1998@gmail.com

Linkedin

https://inlnk.ru/9P1YY

GitHub

https://github.com/trenersem?ta b=repositories

Additional Skills

- React, React router, React hooks, Redux
- JavaScript, DOM, API(ajax, promises, async/await)
- HTML5, CSS3, SASS/SCSS -BEM methodology, Pixelperfect, Cross-browser semantic and adaptive layout -Git,

GitHub, GitLab, NPM, VSCode, SublimeText, Figma,

Photoshop, AdobeXD

Basics of Bootstrap,
 TypeScript

Professional Summary

I'm a 23 years old front-end developer. I am highly motivated and very imaginative by finding inspirations in everyday things, pushing my own boundaries and allowing myself to think out of the box. I am well-versed in React, JavaScript and HTML, CSS. I am a professional grappler, I have won many tournaments. I am fond of fishing and crossfit

Work Experience

11/2021 - Present

Ukraine, Kiev

Front-end Developer (Tokenframe)

10/2018 - 07/2021

Ukraine, Dnipro

Crossfit trainer

Education

2021 - Present

Self Education

- HTML Academy
- LearnJavascript.ru
- Reactjs.org
- Codewars(6 kyu)
- Developer.mozilla.org

2015-2021

DNIPRO STATE MEDICAL UNIVERSITY

Languages

Ukraine — Native Speaker

Russian — Native Speaker

English — B1

Polish — A2

Projects

Portfolio [https://trenersem.github.io/portfolio/] (HTML, CSS, JS, BEM,DOM)

halloween-website (https://trenersem.github.io/halloween-

```
website/halloween-website/index.html)
( HTML, CSS, JS, BEM,DOM)

# plants-website (https://trenersem.github.io/plants-website/)
( HTML, CSS, JS, BEM,DOM)

# Slider(https://trenersem.github.io/Slider/) Stack:
-HTML
-CSS
-JS
```